[Music]
good morning everyone and welcome back
to brainstorm health for a special
session you're hosting this morning
together with our partner McKinsey and
company and we're going to start with a
bold and big vision imagine a world
where the disease burden is cut nearly
in half it's possible according to a new
report from the McKinsey Global
Institute entitled prioritizing health
this report finds that using
interventions in existence today the
global disease burden can be reduced by
40 percent over the next two decades
Amanda's a beautiful vision indeed and
we want to drill down on how we can
reach these goals today there's no
better time to do it than now and no
better person to leave the discussion
and fortune editor-in-chief and my boss
Clifton weed today he's speaking with an
all-star panel
shabam single with McKinsey Amy
McDonough Fitbit mackelmore of Internet
Intermountain Healthcare and as she
suspects Anna from best buy health
before I hand it over to cliff just a
quick note on how you can join the
conversation if you'd like to ask a
question or share a comment enter it
into the chat function on the right side
of your screen once we see it in chat
we'll call on you to come forward so you
can ask your question on camera in order
to do that all you have to do is click
on the share audio and video tab on the
upper right-hand side of your screen and
just as a base of programming note if
you're on camera but not speaking please
mute yourself it just eliminates
background noise and with that I'll hand
things over to Clarence Thank You Ellen
and thank you to all our distinguished
guests for joining us this morning for
all of you I'm thrilled for this
conversation for two reasons the first
is that I have long believed in the
power prevention and early detection and
and really understanding that we can
have a health care system that's not fix
it when it's broke but let's stop it
stop it from breaking the first place so
that's the first reason that I'm excited
accept the challenge has always been
putting numbers on that to putting a
value on I'm doing that hard preventive
work at a time and understanding the
power of social determinants and
on applying that that value so that's
the first reason I'm excited
the second reason I'm excited is that
I'm an optimist and I love silver
linings those how and you know it's
great to think that this curve at 19
offers an opportunity to actually
recreate the health system and get us to
a starting gate that that actually makes
sense for the race we want to run and
with that I am thrilled to ask
shabam of McKenzie who's put together
this absolutely incredible report you
know I just let's start with some big
numbers there's this 12 trillion dollars
in global GDP that we could benefit from
that's a big percent improvement of real
GDP globally and in the u.s. it's about
2.7 trillion if memory serves and that
is a basically a year-over-year basis
that's a point five percent increase in
global global GDP Jomon tell us how you
calculated this and and what did she
highlights about the cordon now thanks
for having me and thanks for the
question so one of the things that we
when we looked at this research the
conversation around healthcare had
really become one of our cost and the
cost of healthcare that's become
unaffordable and runaway and so what we
wanted to understand because if you look
back into the last century the growth in
GDP a lot of it can be traced back a lot
of economic historians have written
about this to the expansion in lifespan
and productivity of the after workforce
what we found was known interventions as
Alan said can can reduce global disease
burden by about 40 percent specifically
what that means if you leave the
technical speaker side is that you know
55 65 could be the new 55 so it is ten
years of healthy and productive life
extension not just life extension but
healthy and productive life
extension and so when you look at that
what that means is that from a
standpoint of premature death so we lose
people early and standpoint aware they
are an ill health and therefore have to
exit the workforce and exit what they
are you know their ability to be
productive we can actually change that
and that 10 years of people being
available to work people being able to
work and and and that is what really
drives the GDP numbers that you said now
by the way just to put this in context
that's the upside of the 12 trillion
dollars that we we talked about the
downside today is so code 19 is gonna
take about an 8% bite out of the global
GDP this year for health takes a 15%
bite out of GDP every year just to put
it in context and that's kind of what
we're really talking about now
final thing I'd say is that the kinds of
intervention that we're talking about
are not rocket science you began this
with prevention more we know what we
have to do with chronic disease burden
and how we can drive you know catching
it early there are very hard behavioural
changes there are communities that we
live in and the health of those that
matter in places like the United States
we've understood the impact of social
factors that drive into influencing a
person's health in lifestyle so there's
a lot that happens about 70% that is
outside of the clinical setting it's
health broadly outside of the clinical
setting that's why I'm excited with you
know some of the colleagues here
including I know a shishun and how we're
thinking about how we engage people
beyond just when they show up to a
doctor or into a hospital yeah you know
it's I'm 56 and I was hoping that 65
would be the new 40 nothing in 50 got it
but but I'll take I'll take you anyway
I've got 10 years to go back to where I
was you know I think that one of the key
key factors as you said is this as
dramatic as the hip GDP is
at 19 it's twice as much at least one
calculated but I you know factoring all
the issues that you factored in it's
twice as much of a hit just in terms of
you know the inefficiencies and the lack
of preparation in the healthcare system
and now you also mentioned four social
determinants these social factors the
communities that we live in zip codes
this increasingly has been the
conversation cage or in healthcare we
really thought starting to see that
well-being isn't just something that's
manufactured in a hospital or clinical
setting but really in the community but
we have a roof over your head whether
it's safe to walk out your street
weather eating well weather you know
access to care all of those things and
and so how is that conversation changing
in your in your mind you know this is
McKenzie you talk to big companies are
they getting this your clients I think I
would say that people are beginning to
get this in the policy circles and
healthcare I think with Kovan 19
everyone is beginning to get this if you
just look at some of the basic
statistics the code 19 and the death
rate has just been higher in
african-american communities for one it
has been higher where people have lower
incomes not a great access to care it
has been a lot higher with people who
are obese or have other underlying
conditions so all of this that we've
been talking about has become extremely
real during this point in time and so if
you just look at whether it's business
leaders in a way that perhaps felt like
an academic conversation sometimes has
become a very real one because we're
seeing a very direct and in a very short
period of time real impact to people's
lives and that is something that we
can't ignore so I'm actually hopeful
that that this becomes a turning point
where many of the things that we were
wearing we've been writing this report
obviously doing the research over a long
period of time and encode 19 just made
it so apparent as to what we what the
what
vulnerabilities are as in the way we
think about health that it is becoming
actually quite relevant today yeah and
Ashish I I actually want to go to you
now because some of this sort of shock
to the system has changed the way
regulators and many people in the larger
and health ecosystem think about what's
possible and think about what should be
so we've seen a you know several orders
that have made you know telemedicine
more feasible giving us billing codes
making more acceptance of telemedicine
and television sits teleconferencing in
general you know for in the health care
setting and and you're going after
invest by a group that historically
hasn't been used to seeing the doctor
that way seniors how is that being
internalized in your in your experience
so uh firstly thank you so much for
having me joined his power you know I
just take one step back and connect to
do what shabam was talking about and the
core of our pieces and best buy it was a
vegetable idea which was that home is
going to become an increasingly
important site of care and covalent for
people spotlight on that in that
paradigm and 15 is the the question
you're asking
but then in particular home be able to
access health in the home is not ever so
more important because of the risk of
infections and or where all the best in
the facility in place environment and to
that extent we have been actively
working with with millions of homes that
we serve where seniors of caregivers the
side and trying to acute no need to be
able to access health care to all sort
of technology solutions what is
fascinating is me how easy it was to
give to contribute homes it does not
take a very complex infrastructure and
being how amiable the environment is to
be able to use these food because there
is just no other alternative and and so
I think at one
which available that is to be the
hardest moving healthcare which is
changing consumer behavior have got
phones to change and then everything
else world is an inlet around that
changing the regulatory construct in the
availability of physicians digitally and
new reimbursement codes is one where all
the various catalyst that they pack
though they're very encouraged we do
think that this is a lasting shift it
may not be found the same levels but but
I'd like you to change the way we access
healthcare so one of the aspects of that
since you know we're comfortable when
the doctor sees us when it's great to be
able to you know have that visual
connection but but we also increasingly
you know will need sensors and devices
to measure things Amy you know I've got
my own Fitbit here and it's you know
that's not a product placement you know
just happening but you know increasingly
learning things that we can do with
these wearable devices that we used to
think of as medical devices I mean I
know that's a dangerous turn on in terms
of FDA regulations have you saying you
know we can check to see if somebody has
atrial fibrillation some very big
studies on that heart rate you know
where do you see the next sort of
dimension for some of these what will we
be able to measure that will bring some
of what I'm shoes and subhan are talking
about him make it reality absolutely so
so cliff is you know you know Kenna
fitments mission has always been 13
years to get healthier and I think what
wearables do as you mentioned has helped
me what was previously invisible visible
to consumers or to members right so
taking something like heart rate that
wasn't really understood or at an
individual level and being able to make
that understandable and it's relatable I
mean it's a metric that now people
and can measure I mean what we're seeing
is that as I mentioned the importance of
whether it's digital digital critical
clinical trials and/or the ability to
bring new kind of early detection of
illness and to the to the rest by the
use of kind of there's these health
metrics one of the most important ways
we're seeing that right now obviously
relates to throw vat19 so based on some
earlier work that we did with Scripps
Research Institute they published some
data in The Lancet looking at data that
was able to take heart health metrics
and being and look those and be able to
then look at early detection and flu and
now what we've done is launched a
clinical trial to be able to look at the
same metrics so heart rate variability
your respiration rate how could those be
early indicators of illness and
obviously knowing just a little bit we
have a lot to learn obviously about poke
at 19 but being able to understand that
the eight you know they're asymptomatic
and pre-symptomatic are really an
important piece and the earlier that you
can catch illness the safer and we can
leave communities and businesses and
education and so that's what we're
really excited about is to be able to to
do that and be able to do that at scale
hey identifying those transmitted
infections that's what often brings
somebody you know not just into the
clinic but often into the emergency room
or you know into some of the expensive
parts of the healthcare we would love to
be able to reinvent
mikkel it's it's great to have you
because you're at the Intermountain
Healthcare which has been a sort of a
leading edge hospital system from health
systems when it comes to invest in the
digital technology investing and I'm
also prevention you know talk a little
bit about you know how you see this this
revolution happening and first whether
you do see that but in some of the stuff
is symbolic has talked about but but but
how do you think you can accelerate and
and thank you to the opportunity to be
here
you know first I do believe this
revolution is happening and like you I'm
an optimist this is a revolution that I
think actually tell it's a big most our
work towards technology driven
healthcare driven us where we at leaders
whose that you know in health care for
those who may not know Rosie imitated
system that has changed the business
model so that we are in a position where
more than 40 percent lives at risk
meaning whether we're health care or not
we're a policeman driving forward a
business model to integrate telehealth
those were providing an exciting in the
rural community which may be who might
not have a critical position or in a
scholarship or limit colleges disease
and need access there and we don't have
been taking the very keen or driven
approach healthcare like creating
hospital where at home primary care and
all of that something of it the
management you know I want to I want to
have a conversation where people can
feel free to jump in a little bit and
can answer each other's questions
shabam I want to talk about one of the
areas that you've zeroed in on which is
cardiovascular disease and that's an
area obviously it's a you know counts
for tremendous amount of mortality in
the US but you pointed out that the
deaths from from heart related illnesses
are about twice as high here in the
United States as they are in Western
Europe you know I always think of Europe
as the sort of home of smoking and
whatnot but but you know what are the
behavior changes that you see that apart
from smoking a you know lack of exercise
that that can can lower that rate here
what is one of the interventions that we
were most excited with I thought was
most feasible you know I think clearly
smoking is an important factor but a
number of the other factors and this is
where healthy lifestyle behaviors really
kind of come in
you mentioned exercise that is that is
known and well proven particularly given
the rate of obesity in the United States
relative to Europe just is much higher
and and that is a precursor to a number
of condition diabetes and cardiovascular
being two of those now that has a lot to
do with a lot that happens before people
show up again into into getting getting
care
cassadee would exercise it has to do
with nutrition by the way on nutrition
there are two different kinds of
problems that we have to deal with one
is just the behaviors and what people
are consuming and how much they're
consuming and how all of that works but
we've also seen on the other side to the
earlier point around social factors
there are people who don't have access
to healthy food right angle or don't
know how to actually then cook at home
and get the right kind of groceries etc
now in this Kovach moment it's
interesting the people have been eating
more at home and going back to a bit
more of the cooking etcetera maybe some
of it was too much baking not as much
healthy cooking but but but but there is
an opportunity to kind of really figure
out there are some health systems who
engaged with their patients and
communities you all probably have seen
with the fresh food pharmacies that they
find work when you is at Geisinger he
started and put in place you've seen
with classes that a number of health
systems are running around helping
people figure out how to make healthy
choices how to do easy to cook recipes
and the like but there's a lot around
nutrition that needs to happen and then
if you look at our healthy environments
you know this one is an interesting one
do we have the right kind of communities
where you can actually get in your
normal day-to-day life a lot more
walking etc to happen do we have the
setups if you will in our offices and
office buildings mostly if you are in
the u.s. in most parts of the US
compared to Europe if you wanted to use
a staircase it's a lot more difficult to
find it and you know let me just
something right there because you know
we're right now obviously all of us are
having this meeting remotely the scores
of people are watching at home or
watching us remotely many of us are not
going to the office unfortunately I am
in the office but don't want to be but
you know we're not getting the kind of
daily exercise that we normally get you
know and so you know you might not hear
henyk mchale you know a name of course
you know this is huge think you're
probably seeing this with your with your
wearable device is actually tracking our
movement maybe what you tell us it's not
true
we've actually seen some really
interesting trends and and just to go
back to what our colleagues are saying
you know it's really about a proactive
approach to health and holistic
well-being around activities sleep
nutrition and mindfulness but you're
right we've been doing a lot of looking
at a population level based on our
thirty million global users and kind of
what's happening with the trends with a
lot of us not you know being out into
the world as much as we typically are
there's been some really interesting
trends one that I'll point out as it
relates to activity is that yes we are
getting less stats we're maybe moving
less throughout the day but our amount
of what I'll call purposeful activity is
actually going up meaning people are
taking that and I know I do this instead
of my commute into the Bay Area and to
San Francisco I'm taking that time and
so we're seeing that that purse
purposeful activity is going up and what
that's resulting in is actually
statistically significant decreases in
things like resting heart rate which is
a real key indicator of health overall
and heart health and so I think while we
all might be eating more sourdough
starter bread and things like that I
think you know we are actually being
mindful around activity our our sleep
our heart rate and I'll and I'll just
add that sleep is another one that we've
had we've seen some increased you know
rest
and more consistency in sleep which is
also important for you know maintaining
community yeah we're seeing some really
interesting trends we know we've got
some awesome questions here but but I
actually have a important question for
you which is about you know many
companies are actually hurting now
financially this is a very very
challenging time as we've seen the 8%
hit - Judy P that shabam mentioned in
the report but do they do companies
actually want to start spending money on
this sort of care at home business that
you that you're selling right now it
takes you know we all seem to invest in
fresh times not any tough times even
though it should be the opposite yes
actually we we have seen a relativist
steadiness in the end and actually an
increase rather than reduction and
that's largely because some of these
solutions have proven to both improve
our counties as well as a reduced cost
and both of those become imperative
these sorts of massive macroeconomic
dispositions and and we get published
peer-reviewed articles just two ways to
quantify the impact of all of that so I
think because it does both of those
things outcomes and cost it actually
comes paradise
no that's great okay Intermountain is an
unusual model and then it sort of owned
the healthcare dollar with your
insurance and so you know you can
actually incentivize the kinds of
behaviors that you bombing Mackenzie's
Mackenzie colleagues that talked about
are you actually seeing money saving
money on this or some space yeah we're
not saving money I think I can speak to
one because adding these through as Liz
just increase utilization what
healthcare services wrong those are now
missing services via telehealth and
we're not finding that we're kinda like
are utilizing Nora help you know it
becomes a part of healthcare now the
weakness of that in our system
when you declare in our system who might
carry telehealth information such as air
goes in collecting health insurance and
used by other parts of the system so
that one visit no offense to another
we're also able to deploy hospital
services in the home and his medical
providers system when were in that
canvass the resources woman in the home
so part of an integrated Ettore increase
health segment I guess I left some
common - there was a question in the
time how these things vary in severity
for people with higher income and other
resources in direct services where and
we did some very more people accessing
services that include something about
designing services for Spanish and
promoted by community organizations that
have trust in middle neighborhoods or in
different ethnic communities in order to
create my same engagement and that's our
well that's a critical issue we want to
bring in yellow and as a partner at
McKinsey Global Institute good morning
you know as what is that part of the
conversation listen I'm an economist by
training and collaborating with Siobhan
and other colleagues who work on the
healthcare industry all the time has
been a real eye-opener for me because a
shoe bomb started saying early on
we have always thought of health as a
potential cost we don't look at the
upside of the economic returns and
really it is that potential for us
at the unique time in the Corbitt
pandemic right now
that we could actually get both better
health and prosperity at the same time
not merely restore the past but really
boost growth over time and that for me
as an economist is a really good message
and I think one that we should have much
more properly not just within the
healthcare community yeah I'd love to
bring in some of these great questions I
mean I think that's a great point
Jana you know too often we think of
health of health spending as a cost in
fact on the PML it shows up as a cause
so you know I think that part of that is
in education to businesses and and you
know community leaders about trying to
show what what you're showing in this
report this terrific report you know I
actually would love to be a fillip jela
I don't know if you want to request that
your camera come on but but your comment
about getting evidence about social
determinants of health and how it how
impactful it is yes we're beginning to
see that payers are recognizing I did
the that paying for these are important
and so starting with for example food
security there is a fair amount of
effort I mentioned an example earlier
that that that is an important part of
improving the numerous of others some of
which as you can imagine are more
connected to healthcare so the nutrition
Anglican see some of these are more
connected to social aspects right and
and things like security just having a
secure environment if you will that we
also have to think about I also tied to
the question that Mark had there around
mental and emotional health that is a
big factor that kind of plays into this
as well the part that obviously connects
quite directly into healthcare is that
is an area that the access to mental
health care is actually quite low and so
there is more investment
you've all kind of seen with with more
government funding etc as well kind of
going in but there's there's a lot more
that needs to be done but Philip is it
yeah sure thank you and I think that
speaks to it and I think the basis of
the question is there's there's evidence
that we're all seeing and I think we all
believe that the social determinants of
health and the predictive and preventive
activities drive down costs the question
is are the people that are currently
bearing the costs willing to invest in
that proactive and as a company that has
a pl cost for health care are they
willing to invest in the preventive
devices and activities to actually help
drive down the cost on the other side in
fact that's a question she's you know I
just want to bring Jennifer Tesla's
question it aligns with that which is
that's by investing the donut place with
some of the technology that you got and
are you seeing any results from oh yes I
think you know point you know one of
identified one doing and it continues to
do is to work with has been provided
with a very simple solution ages ago for
into people's homes tiny sensors and and
data associated with a continued
learning that it's mom taught me joining
the Fed more than usual a she coming
down and go Peter a frigerator number of
times how to you know issue could add to
more often then run from AI algorithms
to do some sort of a predictive
estimation where there is an issue a lot
almost all of air and provider client
actually we do need a dialogue either
working or doing it anything different
places one day by two or using this mean
actually embracing intestines of the
solutions we answer this category yes
that's a good part ii used to connect to
get the question that you have about us
by using it best what has a believable
first employee benefit comes from which
looks at all aspects including physical
security
so and so on and this is this example
that I was thinking of putting of the
blended solution that sensors in
people's homes and and pick up data and
be able to provide me with insights is
yet another little thing that actually
forced to work with other colleagues is
how it would work and does it have about
unique and patents or so I do think that
even you know like many other companies
are self-employed employers for us we
the abilities technology first can be to
the first edition the Google have teamed
up on employees and in actually use the
costume
I just wanted to add there that I think
we're really seeing the player and
providers as well as employers and
education sector really set up and be
interested in both taking a proactive
approach to health by providing tools
and solutions and really holistic
approach and whether that's coaching or
devices or a program that works for them
and to help address the mental health
and attacks that move speaking to
earlier we actually just launched our
ready for work solution which is
combining that really illness detection
that I was mentioning and how your
personal metrics might change if you're
fighting off particularly a viral
illness but also combining that with
mental well-being and emotional health
tools to help individuals kind of going
through this and that's been really well
received by employers and payers who are
looking to really provide those
solutions in a in a safe environment and
and company know along that is that more
questions so actually great ones we we
sure do we've got several on the impacts
on consumers and return I was wondering
if you'd like to to join us and ask your
question about what it means to be self
diagnosing at home at the consumer his
question is when we put diagnostic tools
in the hands of consumers is there a
concern about unintentionally driving up
the public health the health care costs
and the burden on the public health care
system with people self diagnosing
inaccurately
based on both the accuracy of the
technology and proper use of devices or
maybe we're just nervous pee
how are you thinking about helping with
the learning curve for consumer the one
thing the part that I would say on that
is is the point I McHale made earlier
which is this is we have to rethink
health whether it is self enabled care
oh it is clinically provided care and
all that is in between as an integrated
view all right so the ability to have
the Diagnostics a simple view that says
you know maybe there's something that's
going wrong you know or you're not
meeting your goal you didn't work out
enough etcetera those are fine if it
says look your heart rate seems to
become out of whack with what would be
normal
well that should lead to at a minimum a
telehealth cost to your primary care
physician if not to set up and schedule
a visit so I don't think we should view
this as we will just do something at
home then we'll do something in a retail
clinic and then we'll do something in in
in with a doctor it has to be integrated
and the point around the connection of
the data that needs to be across all
these different if you will as Ashish
Burnitz sites of care if home were a
site of care we do need the data to be
believable across all of that and tied
in so that the physician for example if
you have a PCP can look in and say okay
I do need to engage with this person
need to give them a call and have them
come in I think that's what needs to
happen rather than viewing it just as a
you know let let consumers figure it out
on their own you know about 10 minutes
left and we have so many good questions
maybe we could just read some of those
and then also I want to pick me now that
Kenneth Lee mony open fortune is put in
the McKinsey report into our chat room
or those who want to to download it it's
actually live today
so you beating your friends and
neighbors if you download that report
cliff we have a lot of questions about
the business model of how this here's
the great one how do we solve the
conundrum from Syriac reading that there
is much more money to be made in
therapeutics and in prevention and
diagnostic doses there's a cemetery of
diagnostics and prevention startups
everyone's tried and failed what's the
business model what is the solution
please the business model has changed
away we pay for health care we need to
use a model that pays people well I'm a
rather than pays for the diagnostic
treatment care and
risk based models work when we take when
we pay for care per member per month
listening they're incentivized well good
nurse or we need a business model not so
happening for my health care but also
their government you come for a minute
I'm making yeah yeah question that
really speak to that very straight you
know our insurance companies paying for
these kinds of devices just a very quick
point in this the evidence right now to
do that question is if you look at
Medicare Advantage while it's not
perfect it pays for quality experience
and it pays for total cost and most of
the bears as well have much more closely
partnered up with providers to have
providers take on more of the rest of
the point that McKell is just making and
so you actually are beginning to see a
model which is showing that kind of view
and of course anything that can drive
cost cost quality and experience to be
better those in those models are being
paid for and a lot of venture capital
earns companies that do serve into the
Medicare Advantage market so I would say
there's emerging evidence that yes is
the answer to that but sorry Amy you had
a as well thank you I mean I think we
are seeing across the types of plans and
programs integration of devices and a
proactive approach to health so we're
seeing that in commercial business
trying to align a sentence which is what
Nicole was speaking to but also you know
in Medicare and Medicaid
you know incorporating devices to really
empower
across the ecosystem tools to help take
take proactive care to health so I think
we're seeing
sorry not well and he was really
encouraging around where the industry
could go with tighter integration and
better alignment of home incentives so
our last question which will bring us to
an end hopefully will be the most
inspiring one which is about mental
health and stress and work and it seems
to everybody in that cat who's talking
about this use me that we can't make
this work
if we are burned out if we are stressed
and of course we're living in these
incredibly stressful time how what is
the employer work role in all of it it's
a great question who wants to take that
somebody's no wonder about working 20
hours a day for optimism as well Clifton
back to your opening comments that
kool-aid is enabled us to think
differently about the way that we need
support employees in the workplace there
are a lot of positives you know working
from home and ability or hearing from
people regarding work at the intricate
as we go forward into it or be among
Kovach times
we're also knowing access to mental
health has never been like that in our
country and yeah come up with some
creative solution I mean - panting that
time we stood up emotional relief line
we've been able to convert on the health
care that we're providing whenever using
neuropsychiatry Delphic plans we think
those things are going to be really
important for informing the mental
health and poor thing about environment
that produces health and I think these
players are really listening to their
influence right now about what isn't
working we asked many questions
that workhorse about what it's like to
the market meaning and so let's listen
and then redesign the healthcare aspect
that but also the well it's a great time
for thinking definitely you know just
the way it is in healthcare we have an
opportunity to reimagine the future I
think so is the moment to be imagined
how before and at least in the last few
months what we have noticed are two
things 1 positive and 1 we have
preferred the positive part is that
actually amount of work itself has
radically changed you know these are the
times where you don't need to do
anything in the old way that you used to
do it and because of that there is some
newfound efficiency so one is just in
each of the work the quantum of work
itself has has changed and that's been
helpful and I think the challenge that
means facing there by dating all sorts
of interesting ways to solve this is how
do we create serendipity because once
upon a time when we were all in the
offices to walk around and chat and neat
in corridor and new ideas become and
then home clear definitely I think we've
covered a lot today and that was an
inspiring note to end on so thank you so
very much we are going to once again
thank our partner McKinsey for making
this special brainstormed health session
possible along with so many other
wonderful things they make possible in
the world and for us so we will be
seeing you shortly on the mains on the
main stage for our very exciting event
and some wonderful there's some
wonderful stuff coming up cliff I'm
really excited so thank you and we'll
see shortly to everyone thank you
you